<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Graphite</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/index.html</link>
    <description>Recent content on Graphite</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 15:08:43 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Installation</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/installation/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 22:53:31 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/installation/index.html</guid>
      <description>Graphite is available for multiple operating systems, including Linux, macOS, and Windows. Follow the instructions below to install Graphite on your preferred platform.
Linux Installation macOS Installation Windows Installation </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tutorial</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/tutorial/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 15:08:43 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/tutorial/index.html</guid>
      <description>What is Graphite ? : Graphite is a robust desktop application that simplifies the analysis of Excel and CSV files. It allows users to easily convert raw data into meaningful graphs, facilitating well-informed decisions through thorough data visualization.
documentation contenet:
Getting started.
how to acess website. installation. open functionalities:
open file. open folder. new function. new worksheet. open recent. open image. save functionalities:
how to save. save as. data analysis :</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What is New</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/info/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 22:36:57 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/info/index.html</guid>
      <description>Release Notes for Graphite v1.0.0 We are happy to launch our first project, Graphite, which is a data visualizer that will help you create insightful and interactive visualizations from your datasets. This initial release focuses on providing a robust foundation with key features to get you started with data visualization.
New Features Interactive Charts: Create various types of charts (bar, line, pie, etc.) that allow you to interact with your data.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>